

BIRTHDAY:

19/06/1999

NATIONALITY:

ITALIAN

LICENCE:

B

ADDRESS:

Via San Pio X 208 TV 31033 (ITALY)

PHONE:

+39 389 290 3924

EMAIL:

sergioallushaj@gmail.com

SERGIO ALLUSHAJ

I'm a junior web developer with experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, React, and SQL. I'm passionate about creating beautiful and functional websites that provide a great user experience. I'm always learning and growing my skills, and I'm excited to take on new challenges.

EDUCATION

09/2013 - 07/2018

DIPLOMA: AUDIOVISUAL
PRODUCTIONS IPSIA GALILEO
GALILEI

I studied photography both technically and theoretically, learning the photographic language through cinema, art, and history. My training included professional videomaking, covering audio, video, and software equipment for diverse productions such as interviews, commercials, sports events, shows, and documentaries.

05/2023 - ONGOING

WEB DEVELOPMENT AND
DESIGNER COURSE,
ACCADEMIA DELLE
PROFESSIONI, PADUA, ITALY

Studied HTML5, CSS4, JavaScript, and jQuery integration. Applied Bootstrap principles to develop responsive and user-friendly web applications. Emphasized SEO and SEM for site promotion and prototyped interfaces with Figma. Utilized Photoshop, Illustrator and After Effects for design and animation tasks.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021/12 - 2022/08

CUSTOMER SERVICE - STOREDEN (TV)

Dedicated technical assistance to customers: Provide technical support in case of bugs on the Storeden e-commerce platform or on the website. Website customizations: Use of JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Twig, and Bootstrap.

2022/12 - 2023/02

JUNIOR BACK-END DEV - ESOSPHERA (RS)

Web application development using Php (object oriented programming) with Yii2 framework, relational databases and Psql.

2023/05- 2023/10

JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEV - W-EASY

Development and maintenance of websites and management services for companies using the following technologies: JavaScript HTML CSS and PHP.

"I authorize the processing of my personal data contained in the CV in accordance with art. 13 of Legislative Decree 30 June 2003 n. 196 - 'Code regarding the protection of personal data' and art. 13 GDPR 679/16 - 'European regulation on the protection of personal data'

Castelfranco Veneto, 27/06/2024

Segio Allushaj